Last update : 11/16/2022

### 1\. Who are we?

WARGRAPHS is a company offering its users real-time statistics of the game League of Legends. WARGRAPHS is responsible for the processing of your personal data. This data protection policy describes our practices and policy regarding the collection, use and transfer of your personal data. Because we value your trust, we are committed to respecting your privacy by ensuring that your personal data is protected in accordance with data protection regulations.

### 2\. The principles we apply

WARGRAPHS is committed to the following principles in the collection and use of your personal information.

#### 2.1 Legitimate and proportionate use

Personal data are collected, systematically, by WARGRAPHS for determined, explicit and legitimate purposes. The collection of personal data within WARGRAPHS has as a purpose in particular the improvement of services provided. These data may not be used subsequently in a manner incompatible with these purposes. For each processing, WARGRAPHS is committed to collect and process only data strictly necessary for the purpose.

#### 2.2 A fair and transparent collection

In a concern of loyalty and transparency WARGRAPHS takes care to inform the persons concerned of each treatment which it implements by mentions of information. Except for the technical data necessary for the provision of the services, these data are collected fairly and no collection is made without the knowledge of persons and without them being informed. WARGRAPHS is also available at the following address to provide any necessary clarification relating to its personal data protection policy: trebonius@wargraphs.gg

#### 2.3 Adequacy and minimization of collected data

The personal data collected is strictly necessary for the purpose for which it was collected. WARGRAPHS is committed to minimize the data collected, to keep them accurate and up to date. The personal data collected are updated regularly and stored by WARGRAPHS in its databases.

#### 2.4 Personal Data Protection by Design and by Default

WARGRAPHS has adopted internal policies and processes and implements measures that respect the principles of protection of personal data by design and protection of personal data by default. Thus, during the development, design, selection and use of applications, services and products that rely on the processing of personal data WARGRAPHS takes into account the right to the protection of personal data or ensures with their publishers that they meet the legal requirements and ensure the protection of data that will be processed.

### 3\. How do we collect your data?

WARGRAPHS collects personal data that are communicated to it directly in the context of its contractual or pre-contractual relations. It also collects technical data by recording users' interactions with its services and platforms (IP address, dates of connection, pages viewed ...), for example by using cookies. Some data may also be communicated to WARGRAPHS by others which provide and user information. WARGRAPHS may also collect data from affiliated entities, business partners, contractors and service providers if their privacy policies permit.

### 4\. What personal data do we collect?

The term "personal data" refers to any recorded and collected information that directly or indirectly identifies you.

WARGRAPHS processes essentially the following data:

\- IP addresses and browsing details;  
\- Pseudonyms and ID players.  

### 5\. When do we collect your data?

Data is collected by WARGRAPHS on various occasions, including through:

\- the transmission of information from third parties;  
\- Internet activity.  

### 6\. How do we use your data?

WARGRAPHS collects personal data in a lawful manner and in particular:

\- when the person has specifically given consent to it (regarding cookies);  
\- in its legitimate interest;  
\- to comply with legal obligations.  

WARGRAPHS’ legitimate interest is, for instance, to provide a better and personalized service or to improve its services.

### 7\. Who is the recipient your data intended?

Within WARGRAPHS only authorized persons can access personal data when it is necessary for the execution of their missions. Some data may be sent to third parties to meet legal, regulatory or contractual obligations or to legally authorized authorities. We may also share personal data with other parties, including the companies and third parties like service providers and subcontractors providing services or features on behalf of WARGRAPHS.

### 8\. How long do we keep your data?

WARGRAPHS retains personal data for as long as is necessary for the purposes for which it was collected or to comply with its legal retention obligations, according to the following table:  
IP adresses: Browsing data 7 days from last activity  
Pseudonyms and players: ID 10 years from last connection on RIOT GAMES

### 9\. What cookies do we use?

WARGRAPHS collects data through cookies and other similar technologies (trackers). Cookies are text files that are automatically copied to your computer and mobile device when you visit a website. These files are stored by the browser. These cookies contain basic information about the person's use of the Internet. The browser sends these cookies to WARGRAPHS’ websites and platforms each time they are visited so that the computer or mobile device is recognized and the browsing experience is personalized and enhanced. It is possible to control cookies with browser settings and other tools, however, refusing to install a cookie may result in the inability to access certain services.

### 10\. What are your rights?

In accordance with data protection regulations, you have the following rights concerning your personal data:

\- right of access (right to request access to your data and to obtain confirmation from WARGRAPHS that it is processing your data) ;  
\- right to rectification (right to modify or complete its data when they are inaccurate or incomplete) ;  
\- right to deletion (right to request the deletion of its data from the processing) ;  
\- right to restriction of processing (right to request the limitation of the processing of one's data) ;  
\- right to data portability (right to request the transfer of one's data to oneself or to another data controller) ;  
\- right to object (right to object to certain processing operations, especially those for marketing purposes) ;  
\- the right to appeal to a data protection authority (CNIL).  

The exercise of these rights by a person is done by proving his identity (e.g. copy of your identity card signed) by mail to the following address: trebonius@wargraphs.com or the online form on the institutional site of WARGRAPHS: www.leagueofgraphs.com or porofessor.gg. Requests to exercise rights are processed for tracking and proof purposes and are kept for 5 years. Despite the exercise of the right of deletion WARGRAPHS is required to retain certain data as evidence in the event of litigation or because of its legal obligations.

### 11\. Right to withdraw your consent at any time

In case your data is only collected according to your consent, you have the right to withdraw your consent at any time. The withdrawal of consent shall not affect the lawfulness of processing based on consent before its withdrawal.

### 12\. How do we protect your data ?

WARGRAPHS attaches a significant importance to the security of personal data. It has put in place technical and organizational measures adapted to the degree of sensitivity of the personal data, in order to ensure the integrity and confidentiality of the data and to protect them against any malicious intrusion, any loss, alteration or disclosure to unauthorized third parties. Thus, it undertakes to take the physical, technical and organizational security measures necessary in order to :

\- protect its activities ;  
\- preserve the security of the personal data of its members, partners, Internet users, suppliers and service providers ;  
\- against any unauthorized access, modification, distortion, disclosure, destruction or access to the personal data it holds.  

Nevertheless, the security and confidentiality of personal data depends on the good practices of each person, so the person concerned is invited to remain vigilant on the issue. In accordance with its commitments, WARGRAPHS chooses its subcontractors and service providers with care and requires them to :

\- a level of protection of personal data equivalent to its own ;  
\- use of personal data or information only to ensure the management of the services they must provide ;  
\- strict compliance with applicable laws and regulations regarding confidentiality, banking secrecy and personal data ;  
\- the implementation of all appropriate measures to ensure the protection of personal data that they may be required to process ;  
\- the definition of technical and organizational measures necessary to ensure security.  

WARGRAPHS undertakes to conclude with its subcontractors in accordance with legal obligations contracts defining precisely the terms & conditions of personal data processing.

### 13\. External links

Our website and platform may include links to third-party websites, plug-ins and applications. The operators of these sites may collect or share information about their visitors. This information will be used by those operators in accordance with their privacy policies, which may differ from this Privacy Policy. Individuals are encouraged to read those privacy policies and to refer directly to those third parties if they have questions about their practices.

### 14\. Changes to this Privacy Policy

We may modify, update and/or replace this Privacy Policy in particular in case of changes in data protection regulations. We recommend that you consult this Privacy Policy regularly to ensure that you are aware of the latest version.

### 15\. How to contact us?

If you have any questions or requests regarding WARGRAPHS’ handling of personal data, please send an e-mail to trebonius@wargraphs.gg or use the online form on WARGRAPHS’ corporate website: www.leagueofgraphs.com or porofessor.gg.

### 16\. Advertising

This Site is affiliated with CMI Marketing, Inc., d/b/a Raptive (“Raptive”) for the purposes of placing advertising on the Site, and Raptive will collect and use certain data for advertising purposes. To learn more about Raptive’s data usage, click here: [https://www.cafemedia.com/publisher-advertising-privacy-policy](https://www.cafemedia.com/publisher-advertising-privacy-policy)
